Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5685
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XII: Financial Records, 1939-1974
  - Sub-Series D. Local's Financial Records, 1943-1974
    - Financial statements, auditor's reports, and financial info (Box 173, Folder All)
    - Financial statements and auditor's reports, 1945-1967 (Box 174, Folder All)
      Locals 160, 165, 201 and 206
    - Financial statements and auditor's reports for Local 206, 1954-1972 (Box 175, Folder All)
    - Financial statements and auditor's reports, 1942-1974 (Box 176, Folder All)
      Locals 28, 211, 295, 333, 370, 475, 501, 700
    - Financial statements and financial information (Box 177, Folder All)
      Regarding the Employer's Council and Local 64 Trust Fund
    - Financial statements and financial information (Box 178, Folder All)
    - Dues sheets for Locals 48,80, 88 and related companies (Box 179, Folder All)
    - Work cards for Local 64, 1946-1960 (Box 180, Folder All)
    - Work cards for Local 64, 1946-1960 (Box 181, Folder All)
    - Dues Sheets & Pension & Welfare Sheets (Box 182, Folder All)
      Locals 201 & 202
    - Dues sheets for Locals 64, 85, 88, 1960-1970 (Box 183, Folder All)
      Hudson Bay Company
    - Dues sheets for Locals 27, 63, 85, 88, 112, 200, 1948-1969 (Box 184, Folder All)
- Series XIII: Legal Files, 1955-1973
  - Sub-Series A. Legal Files - General, 1955-1958
    - Eberle Tanning Co., 1967-1971 (Box 185, Folder 1-2)
    - Fur Merchants Employees Council, 1955-1958 (Box 185, Folder 3-4)
  - Sub-Series Housing: See - next box, ff 1-7, 1964-1973
    - Hudson Bay Co., 1965 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Industrial Electrical Contractors Association, 1964 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Levor, G. & Co., 1967 (Box 185, Folder 7-8)
    - Mutual Sewing Machine Dealers Association, 1957-1961 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - New York Auction Co., 1959-1965 (Box 185, Folder 10-11)
    - Housing, 1962-1969 (Box 186, Folder 1-7)
    - New York Fur Cleaners Assn., 1959-1965 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Rabbit Dressers Institution, 1958-1960 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Resina Automatic Machinery, 1962-1965 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Shoe Factory Cases, 1968-1969 (Box 186, Folder 11-12)
    - Silberman Fur Corp., 1944-1946 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Silk Association, 1948-1957 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Singer Sewing Machine Co., 1961-1973 (Box 187, Folder 3-5)
    - Steamfitter Local, 1966 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Tariff -, 1955-1960 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - United Mineral & Chemical Corp., 1964-1968 (Box 187, Folder 8-10)
    - United Mineral & Chemical Corp., 1964-1965 (Box 188, Folder 1-5)
    - Miscellaneous, - Includes some reports & miscellaneous files, 1957-1967 (Box 188, Folder 6-10)
      re Joint Board legal matters
  - Sub-Series B. Realty Files
    Arranged by location/address
    - Legal documents & correspondence re real estate taxes, income, etc. (Box 189, Folder All)
- Series XIV: Printed Material
  - Sub-Series A. Organizing Campaign Materials
    Arranged by company name. Includes announcements, broadsides, miscellaneous correspondence, form letters, clippings, newsletters, transcripts of radio broadcasts, and miscellaneous.
    - Allied Kind Co., Wilmington, Delaware, 1966 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Bird In Hand Poultry Company, Lancaster, Pennsylvania, 1963 (Box 190, Folder 2-3)
    - Bucilla, Division of Carlsbrook Industries, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 190, Folder 5-6)
      Long Island City, New York
    - Cannery Campaign, 1960 (Box 190, Folder 7-13)
      Includes campaign 5 at Hungerford Packing, Hungerford, Pennsylvania, Krouse Foods Inc., Peach Glen, New York, Chas. G. Summers Inc., New Freeham, Pennsylvania, Hanover Canning Co, Hanover, Pennsylvania and others
    - Eastern Molded Co., Clearfield, Pennsylvania, 1970 (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Endicott-Johnson, Endicott, New York, 1944-1959 (Box 190, Folder 15-17)
    - Greenwood Food Inc., Waterloo, New York, 1965 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Levor & Co., Gloversville, New York, 1955 (Box 190, Folder 19-21)
    - Loewengart & Co., Mercersberg, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 190, Folder 22-23)
    - May's, Inc., New York, New York, 1980 (Box 190, Folder 24)
    - Parker Hannifin, Lyons, New York, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 25-26)
    - Pocahontas Tanning Co., Frank, West Virginia, 1969 (Box 190, Folder 27)
    - Saco Tanning Corp., Scarborough, Maine, 1969 (Box 190, Folder 28)
    - Weingarten, ?, 1961 (Box 190, Folder 29)
    - Weis Markets, York, Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign materials (Box 191, Folder 1-2)
  - Sub-Series B. Publications & other misc. documents
    - American Hide & Leather - newspaper clippings re strike, 1946 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Benefit booklets from union members (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Broadsides (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Cartoons (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Endicott Johnson, "Partners All" (bd. vol.) (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - Frankfurt Fair (Publications) (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - "If Not Now...When?" (Box 191, Folder 9)
      Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen
    - King, Martin Luther - Miscellaneous publications (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - "Meat cutters" (Box 191, Folder 11)
      (Series of articles appearing in Herald News, New Jersey)
    - Schools - Potosi (Box 191, Folder 12-17)
      information re summer school for workers
    - Schools - Southwest Leadership Schools (Box 191, Folder 18-19)
    - Shop Action Bulletin on the trial of President Gold (2 issues) (Box 191, Folder 20)
    - "Ten Years for Peace & Democracy" (Box 191, Folder 21)
      Joint Board Fur Dressers & Dyers, n.d.
    - "Things You Should Know About The International Fur & (Box 191, Folder 22)
      ...Leather Workers Union..."
    - "Victory Will Be Ours!" unpaged, n.d. IFLWU (Box 191, Folder 23)
    - "We Ask Justice For Our Union Leaders!" (Box 191, Folder 24)
      IFLWU, n.d., 32 pp.
    - Westfield Leather Workers Bulletin (Box 191, Folder 25)
      (Westfield, Pennsylvania) 1 issue, no date
    - Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 26-30)
      includes publications, broadsides and other miscellaneous documents
    - Cash Book -, 1932-1935 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook [very brittle] (Box 206, Folder 1)